Isn't that P'Big Jane?
I'm sorry for everything.
You are my new dream.
Will you marry me?
Sure.
Jane, stay with me!
Jane, wake up and talk to me first.
I'd give up anything for you, Jane.
Who are you?
The condition Jane is experiencing
a state where a patient loses memories
due to brain trauma.
He can only remember
before he started his second year of university.
Then you probably don't remember
that we were seeing each other for a while?
If you still can't remember me...
I will make you fall in love with me all over again.
How are you?
Huh.
I'm ok mom.
But...
Why is our home...
You sold the house to him.
Why?
I was the one who caused trouble.
I got our family into ten million baht of debt.
P'Jane helped by buying the house
and giving me the money to pay off the debt.
If he wanted to help,
why did he have to kick you out of the house?
Why did he make your family
have to live in a place as rundown as this?
I will buy this house...
I didn't kick them out.
Jane was the one who decided to move out on his own.
I don't believe you.
Why would Jane do something like that?
Ah!
Ouch!
Stop!
Jane?
Jane!
Ah!
Are you alright?
Jane is probably exhausted now.
You should head back first.
In that case, I'll take my leave.
Goodbye, P'Jane.
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Ooh
When it comes to treatment,
I've done everything I can.
Does that mean
Little Jane will have to be like this forever?
It's not like that.
I just want you to take it easy.
With cases like this, sometimes it takes months,
and for some, it takes over a year
for all their memories to return.
But I can't take this anymore.
Isn't there any way to make
Little Jane remember faster?
To be honest, there is a way.
Maybe..
you might need to take him to places,
events,
or meet people associated with the memories he forgot.
Who knows, doing something like this
might make his memories come back faster.
But let me warn you about one thing,
I can't guarantee how that goes.
For some people, doing this
might cause them to go into shock,
or they might not be able to accept
the self that they had forgotten.
Either way...
just take it slow and start gently first.
I had no idea
you liked taking photos, P'Dan.
You ask just like back in our university days,
back when
you came to help me out at the academic fair.
Really?
I'm sorry...
that I can't remember.
Why are you apologizing to me?
Well...
for you,
it feels like it haven't happened yet, right?
Let me take a photo of you.
Why?
Come on, I won't sell it like last time.
What did you say?
Nothing!
Come on.
Give it a try.
One, two...
Ooh,
looks nice!
This one...
Whoa...
Hey.
Do I really look that old, P'Dan?
Mm...
Suddenly having five years added to your age
without realizing it,
it probably feels something like this.
But if you ask me,
you're still not as old as I am.
Hahaha!
Let me get one more shot,
a redo.
Let's try again.
One, two...
(Mr. Jane Patrick Terry Palakorn)
So is there something you want to tell me about?
About your age?
And about Harvard?
Uh...
Jane,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
Jane, I think
this angle looks great.
Let's take a selfie together.
Here we go.
One, two...
Look at the camera.
The background looks nice, see?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
One more photo.
One, two...
Here.
You don't look old, see?
Whoa...
Here.
What are you guys doing?
Getting ready to live stream selling herbs.
There's this much of it?
Yeah.
It's really trending right now.
And those herbal sachets you came up with,
they are super popular.
Jane.
I'll get the door.
Is there anything I can help with, Jean?
Hello, P'Jane.
Come on in.
Hello.
Hello uncle and auntie.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm coming to ask for permission
to take Jane to my place today.
I'm not letting him go.
Calm down first.
Well, I'm just worried that something
might happen to Jane again.
I feel the same way.
And I think that right now,
he shouldn't go anywhere.
But I've already consulted with P'Ram
regarding Jane's condition.
P'Ram said
that if Jane encounters situations
or people from the period he forgot,
it might help trigger his memories to come back.
So that's why you came
to pick my brother up, right, P'Jane?
Yes.
Besides,
there's someone I want Jane to meet.
It's up to you, Jane.
If you're not ready yet, it's okay.
Teach me.
I want to draw a race car.
I want to go.
Jane...
We're worried about you, you know?
But it's the only way that can help Jane, you know.
You should know
that we...
As for the person who crashed into the car last time,
I currently have a police acquaintance
looking into it.
It won't be long,
we should be able to identify the person behind it.
Don't you want Jane to regain his memories?
Please?
Please let him go.
I can tell
that my brother doesn't want to stay
like this forever either.
Please?
I don't want to be a burden to everyone.
I want to remember everything again.
We're here, this is my house...
the house we used to live in together.
Hello,
Mr. Little Jane.
Hello.
You are...
It's Auntie May.
It's so wonderful to have you back.
Ever since you left,
Mr.Jane hasn't seemed lively at all.
Where is Jamie, Auntie May?
He's upstairs.
He'll be down in a moment.
In that case, I'll go call him down, okay?
Sure.
Jane...
Did you know
where the dining room was?
I didn't know.
I just felt like...
it had to be this way.
Lil' Jane...
Do you remember...
me?
Jane...
Jane? Do you remember Jamie?
I don't remember yet,
but I can really feel it..
that you must be someone very important.
You draw so well.
That's because Lil' Jane is a good teacher!
Then will you teach me again?
Of course.
How about we draw a bird?
Sure.
Then...
let's start with the outline first,
and then draw the face.
I'm sorry...
that I still can't remember.
Why are you apologizing?
It's not your fault at all.
I'm just happy
to see you bright and lively while drawing again.
It reminds me of you back in university.
Well...
I am still in university.
That's true.
So...
what was I like when I was working?
When you worked, you looked quite happy.
Probably because you were close to me.
Though you still couldn't say no
to other people as usual.
Well...
sounds just like me.
Come over here.
There's something I want to show you.
Jane?
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Jane?
Let go of me!
Gap,
explain to me why I had to wear
a student uniform too?
I look too old for this!
And Khing didn't even show up!
Stop complaining.
It's to help bring back Jane's memories.
Just help out.
You still look good though.
Yeah.
Yeah, Jane, so how are you doing?
Thanks a lot, guys,
for doing all this for me.
I'm going to invite P'Big Jane over too.
He should be here soon.
I really want to know...
am I actually dating P'Jane?
Can you tell me about
back when we first started dating?
Sure.
Though we don't know a whole lot, to be honest.
From what we saw,
you and P'Jane took a bunch of classes together,
so you two became really close.
And P'Dan?
P'Dan
came along right around the time
you and P'Jane took a break.
But that was super brief,
you dumped him
and went right back to P'Jane.
Holy crap...
did I really do all that?
And...
what was P'Jane like
back in our university days?
Not many people dared to mess with him, honestly.
Yeah, for real.
And there were always weird rumors
going around about him,
like...
like he was some kind of demon or something,
where you could make a contract
to ask for anything,
but when he came to collect the debt,
your life could get completely ruined, you know?
Why are you saying things that'll make him
scared of P'Jane?
My boss takes exceptionally good care of him, okay?
Gosh, look at you, so devoted to your boss!
Well!
Of course! He's a good person!
Back in our uni days,
Put was trying so hard
to keep P'Jane away from Jane.
Oh, yeah!
Speaking of Put,
I haven't seen him at all since I woke up.
Where did he go?
Well...
Oops!
Holy shit! Uh...
Hey!!
Huh?
That was a miss.
Gap, what the hell are you doing?
Guess my aim is off today.
My feet are getting tired.
Could you go get that for me?
Please? I'm...
Yeah, I'm exhausted.
Please, please go pick it up for me!
Go get it for me, please!
Alright, alright.
You're the sweetest!
Can I have the ball back, please?
Can I have the ball back, please,
so we can keep playing.
Jane,
I'm sorry
about what happened at my house yesterday.
I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
I'm sorry too, P'Jane,
for not listening to you at all...
even though you were just trying to help me.
It was my fault.
Honestly,
I should have started with something small first.
So...
what should we start with today?
Back in uni,
we used to sit and write reports
together at this table.
This was our usual spot.
Really?
What are you doing?
Are you cold?
Do you remember, Jane?
Whoa!
Gap!
Fahsai!
Salmon!
Pai!
Damn.
P'Jane really went all out.
Whoa.
Hey.
Loma.
First.
Long time no see!
Oops!
How are you doing, Little Jane?
Still as tiny as ever!
Ouch!
Doing well, right?
Little Jane?
Yes! Little Jane!
Just listen and go along with it dude,
you'll understand soon.
Professor, don't go spoiling it just yet.
Oh! Oops!
Owh!
Babes!
Let's take attendance now, shall we?
Come gather around everyone!
Let's start class.
You're Jennalee, right?
Yes.
In the last class, you took sick leave,
so I had everyone pair up,
and everyone is taken already.
But that's totally fine.
We have another special student
joining us for their first day today as well.
There's your dance partner.
Jane Patrick.
Ahem!
Okay, everyone!
Um,
you're... uh...
Jennalee, right?
And you are Jane Patrick.
Oh!
You have the same name.
I'll just give you a new nickname.
so it's easier for me to call you.
You're still as tiny as ever,
so let's call you Little Jane, okay?
As for you...
gosh, you're still as big and tall as ever!
Ah, I'll call you Big Jane  then.
Little Jane will dance as the lady,
and Big Jane as the gentleman.
Hahaha, tiny one!
Little one, little one!
Alright, pair up now!
Pair up! Gap!
Turn to your partner!
May I dance with you?
Alright, I'm going to start counting the rhythm now.
Take it nice and easy.
Count...
One, two, three, go!
One, two, three...
Very good! Keep going!
Do you remember anything at all?
I still don't remember...
but...
it feels like my body is just moving on its own.
Alright, everyone, get ready to turn!
When you turn, remember to shift
your weight onto the other leg.
This is the condo where we lived
together during university.
It's this luxurious?
I'm sorry, P'Jane...
um...
I don't like eating ginkgo nuts.
I know.
But try just one bite.
I put my all into making it.
It's not bitter at all.
How did you do that, P'Jane?
I knew
you disliked them because of the bitter taste,
so I secretly went and found a way
to make them easy for you to eat.
Thank you.
I have one more thing...
Please have some cake with me.
Today happens to be my birthday.
Today is your birthday, P'Jane?
I'm so sorry...
that I didn't remember.
It's alright.
How could I ever be angry with you?
Happy birthday, P'Jane.
Is there anything you want for your birthday?
I want you.
Uh...
I want my old Jane back.
It's okay, Jane.
It doesn't matter if you still can't remember.
I'll always be right here with you.
You play the piano so well, P'Jane.
You once asked me
if I didn't run a business
what my dream would be.
So I told you
that when I was a kid,
I dreamt of becoming a pianist.
Want to give it a try?
I don't know how to play.
Ah.
P'Jane.
Before you lost your memory,
we promised each other that...
we were going to get married.
I'll wait for you, Jane.
What if you have to wait forever?
Even if it's forever, I'll still wait.
But I don't want to hold you back.
I'm in so much pain.
I feel so guilty that...
I can't remember anything at all..
that I couldn't even remember your special day...
I don't even remember
how we fell in love.
How am I supposed to be a good partner
to you like this?
And I'm scared...
None of this feels like my life at all.
I'd give anything.
Just please...
Jane, don't leave me.
I'm willing to give up everything I have.
I can even stop running favors.
Can you just stay with me for now?
I'm sorry...
Jane.
When you said you loved me,
or were you just saying it?
Because what you did makes it so clear
You tricked me into loving you,
and then you destroyed me
You said you loved me,
yet you hurt me
The more I love you,
the more it hurts
I just want to know,
did you ever love me?
Jane.
P'Dan?
How did you get here?
I went to your apartment.
Your mom said you were here.
Did he do something to you?
Want to go home?
I'll can take you home.
I won't let Jane go anywhere.
Jane wants to leave.
Stop forcing him.
Then stop sticking your nose
into my business with Jane.
This is one thing I have to butt into.
I won't let Jane stay anywhere near
a dangerous person like you.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Is that a threat?
You threatened Put the exact same way, didn't you?
Put?
What happened?
Jane.
Jane, stay calm.
But I really have to tell you this
so you'll stop getting involved with him for good.
Put is...
Hey.
Hey!
Stop!
Stop!! Jane, don't listen to him!
I can explain this!
Stop!
P'Dan!
Speak!
Put is dead
and he is
the one behind Put's death!
You told me yourself.
It's not true.
Jane, you know I didn't do it.
Jane!
Go!
Don't...
Jane!
(P'Dan)
To P'Jane,
I've read the letter you left for me.
It took me quite a while before
I could bring myself to write a reply.
Though I'm not sure
if I'll ever get the chance
to give it to you to read.
Can I have the ball back?
So we can keep playing?
Our contract is complete.
I will never let you go again.
Thank you for coming back into my life, Jane.
Thank you for not giving up on someone like me.
Marry me.
Where are you rushing off to?
I'll be right back.
Even up until now,
I am still confused
about whether I should believe you.
Even so,
there is one thing I am completely sure of
that I still love you, P'Jane, always.
No matter how much time passes.
Huh?
Hey. Jet?
Where is he going?
I'm going to P'Jane's house!
I remember everything!
Really?
Yeah.
Let me take you!
And the love that I have for you
And the love I have for you
is far greater than any reason.
Thanks Jet.
Good luck!
Yeah.
It is what brought me to write
to you in this letter.
Auntie May!
Oh, Mr. Little Jane!
Auntie May,
where is P'Jane?
Calm down first.
Mr.Jane is over by the poolside over there.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Huh?
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for your ten reasons.
Thank you for loving me just the way I am.
P'Jane.
And most importantly.
Thank you for allowing me to continue
being this emotional person.
I remember now.
I love you.
From Little Jane..
who belongs to Big Jane.
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I remember everything.
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Welcome home, Jane.
Anyone can tell me you're trouble
But being with you feels like paradise
I’ll be yours forever
Or maybe I’m just out of my mind
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
I just can't resist it,
Oh Oh
When it comes to you, I can't hold back,
Because you're the only one I love, it’s you
I've surrendered my whole heart, For you
The more I try to stop, the more I love you,
love you like this.
I can't stop loving you at all
Oh Oh
Everyone got to follow their dreams.
It's so great that everything ended well, right?
There's still one more person
who hasn't followed their dream yet.
I love you, Jane.
Let's stay together forever.
Yes!
Thank you for always staying by my side.
I told you I'm resting.
Don't call to disturb me.
Something terrible has happened.
It's... Mr.Jamie...
What?!
Lil' Jane!
Then let me go with you.
I won't let you put yourself at risk.
Jamie!
I just can't resist it,
oh oh
When it comes to you, I can't hold back,
Because you're the only one I love,
it’s you
I've surrendered my whole heart,
For you
The more I try to stop, the more I love you,
love you like this.
I can't stop loving you at all
Oh Oh
Everyone says that you're dangerous
That you never care about anything,
but I’m fine
The more I understand your heart
The more my own heart trembles
oh oh
You made me understand the meaning of love
The way you look at me
is like a breeze blowing in
Making me feel, feel, feel
When you tell me you love me every day,
every night, every night
I used to think about giving up,
but my heart told me to try
I tried to force myself not to love you,
but can't stop now
I just can't resist it,
oh oh
When it comes to you,
I can't hold back,
oh oh
Because you're the only one I love,
it’s you
I've surrendered my whole heart,
For you
The more I try to stop, the more I love you,
love you like this.
I can't stop loving you at all
I wanted to change my mind,
to go back, to repent,
to stop loving you
But I can't.
It gets further away, yet closer,
and I keep missing you
Because you're here,
I'll hold you close
I won't let you go anywhere, 'Cause you're the only one
I used to think about giving up,
but my heart told me to try
I tried to force myself not to love you,
but can't stop now
I just can't resist it,
oh oh
When it comes to you, I can't hold back,
Because you're the only one I love,
it’s you
I've surrendered my whole heart,
For you
The more I try to stop, the more I love you,
love you like this.
I can't stop loving you at all